[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Troy gives Gabriella a necklace in High School Musical 2.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Schnapps is a kind of fruit brandy and is typical for the country which gave the name of this beverage.", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Italy", "The Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "My husband came downstairs dressed for work, thus setting off my coulrophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Clowns", "incorrect_answers": ["Hair gel", "Uniforms", "Ties"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Goonies, when Andy goes into one of the dark caves, who does she kiss?", "correct_answer": "Mikey", "incorrect_answers": ["Brand", "Mouth", "Data"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As depicted in the Soylent Green science fiction movie, what was not a reason for the food crisis in 2022?", "correct_answer": "Volcanic explosions", "incorrect_answers": ["Global warming", "Yellow smog", "Plant and animal species destroying"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these US states is not named after a river?", "correct_answer": "Iowa", "incorrect_answers": ["Illinois", "Alabama", "Colorado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of these achievements did Sir Alexander Flemming win the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine in 1945?", "correct_answer": "the discovery of penicillin", "incorrect_answers": ["the discovery of the enzyme lysozyme", "the introduction of the smallpox vaccine", "developing a process which slows microbial growth in foods"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these games of skill and strategy has a pen and pencil version, played on a field of 8x10 boxes?", "correct_answer": "Soccer", "incorrect_answers": ["Volleyball", "Pool", "Baseball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This composer hired cliquers to boo his sons early works at their premier. Eventually, the popularity of his sons works overcame the insults of the father and his stooges. Name the father.", "correct_answer": "Johann  Strauss", "incorrect_answers": ["Johannes Brahms", "Johan Sebastian Bach", "Franz Lizst"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Sid from Ice Age 3 gets jealous of Manny and Ellie, what does he adopt?", "correct_answer": "Three abandoned eggs", "incorrect_answers": ["Scrat", "Three baby sloths", "A mammoth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He first developed the principle of relativity.", "correct_answer": "Galileo", "incorrect_answers": ["Michelson-Morley", "Einstein", "H.A. Lorentz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chihuahuas come in three colors: brindle, black, and camel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]